mypetwarehouse.com.au 2012-06-12

# Privacy Policy - My Pet Warehouse

|   
---|---  
  
**What Personal Information About Customers Does My Pet Warehouse Gather?**  
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve the shopping experience at My Pet Warehouse. Here are the types of information we may gather.

  * **Information You Provide Us:** We receive and store any information you may enter on our website or provide to us via other methods. This information may include names, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses etc. Website activity and history such as; searches, purchases, incomplete orders, review postings, and emails sent to My Pet Warehouse may also be collected. You can choose not to provide certain information, this may however limit your ability to take advantage of the many features our website can offer. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, fulfilling orders, customizing future shopping for you, improving our store features and also to communicate further with you.
  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our website. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies" to store certain types of information about your visit to our website, this information can be recalled when your web browser accesses our website.
  * **E-mail Communications:** The majority of online order correspondence is carried out via email as this is typically the most convenient method of touching base with our customers and advising the current status of any online order. In the event of a change to any of our online policies email may be used to notify you of these changes. From time to time we also use this method of communication to send out an optional newsletter advising you of any special promotions, services and or products we have to offer. * If you do not wish to receive these promotional emails, (i.e. emails other than order notifications and receipts) please adjust your "Mailing List" preferences by logging into your account. 

**More About Cookies?**  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifier text files that we transfer to your computer's web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits etc.

**Does My Pet Warehouse Share Any Information It Receives?**  
We respect your privacy and appreciate your business. At no time do we ever provide your account contact or payment information to any third party vendor, associate or service provider unless absolutely necessary in order to complete your transaction and order.

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**  
We work to protect the security of any sensitive information you may transmit to us by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption. During payment processing and also within other secure areas of our website this Secure Layer encrypts the information you provide to us. Only the last few digits of your credit card number is stored after placing an order, we do however transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card processor or merchant during payment, again this information is encrypted to avoid risk. Whilst we maintain steps to protect your data it is important for you to also protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when you have finished using a shared computer by clicking the "log off" link located at the top of the website.

**Which Information Can I Access?**  
My Pet Warehouse gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with us for the limited purpose of viewing, and in certain cases, updating that information. A detailed history of previous transactions linked to your account is also accessible.

**Conditions of Use, Policies, and Revisions**  
If you choose to visit My Pet Warehouse, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of our local state. If you have any concern about privacy of your personal information as used and collected within our website, please send us a thorough description of your concerns and we will do our best to try to resolve the matter.

It is important to realise that our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Policy and Conditions of Use may change accordingly. Although periodic reminders of our policies and conditions may be emailed to you (unless you have instructed us not to) we recommend reviewing our website policies from time to time to ensure any changes to these policies and conditions are understood and agreed to. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

**Questions**  
Questions regarding our Conditions of Usage, Privacy Policy, or other policy related material can be directed to our support staff by clicking on the "Contact Us" link found in our menu. Or you can email us directly at: [sales@mypetwarehouse.com.au](mailto:sales@mypetwarehouse.com.au)

My Pet Warehouse knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust and want you to feel confident in our services and security as it relates to your personal information. This policy describes our privacy policy. By visiting My Pet Warehouse, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**Common Search Terms:** [Pet Supplies Online](http://www.mypetwarehouse.com.au/) | Pet Accessories | Pet Food | Pet Products | Pet Supplies | Pet Grooming | [MyPetWarehouse](http://www.mypetwarehouse.com.au/about) | [Online Pet Store](http://www.mypetwarehouse.com.au/) | [Pet Barn](http://www.mypetwarehouse.com.au/pet-barn)   
Dog Collars | Dog Food | Dog Accessories | Dog Supplies | Dog Grooming | [Petbarn](http://www.mypetwarehouse.com.au/pet-barn) | Cat Supplies | Cat Food | Cat Grooming | Vet Supplies | Pet Care

Copyright © MyPetWarehouse 2012 all rights reserved. A.B.N. 21 620 597 911. All prices listed are in AUD and include GST.  
Prices and specifications are subject to change without notice. E&OE.
